ROBERTO ROMERO MARTÍN

JUNIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER



robertoromerodeveloper@gmail.com

York, England

https://roberromero.github.io/my-portafolio/

in www.linkedin.com/in/roberto-romero-martin

PROFILE

I am a qualified and professional web developer with experience in website design. Strong creative and analytical skills. I am currently building Apps to learn how to use efficiently Redux and Node.js. In addition to the technologies that I use on a daily basis and that appear in the header, I am also familiarised with technologies such as XML, XHTML, JUnit, JQuery, Ajax, Java, C#, XAMPP, etc.

SKILLS

HTML5
CSS3
JavaScript
React
PHP
MySQL

SOFT SKILLS

- Teamwork.
- · Problem-Solving.
- Communication.
- · Ability to change.
- Languages: Spanish and English.

EDUCATION

DEVELOPMENT OF WEB APPLICATIONS

Diploma of Higher Education Ilerna Online 2020-2022

ENGLISH, LANGUAGE AND CULTURE

Degree UNED 2016-2020

EXPERIENCE

OXYGEN WORKSPACE

Madrid, Spain 2022 (Apprenticeship)

- Creating websites using: HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React.
- Working with Programmers and Web Designers to create a website that matches the visual design intent under the supervision of a CTO.
- Communicating with business colleagues to gather and refine requirements and specifications for content development within agreed-upon timelines. Git, GitHub and Slack were used.
- Agile Scrum Methodology was used.

OJALÁ SPANISH ACADEMY DIRECTOR

https://ojala-spanishacademy.co.uk/

York, England

2012 - Present

- Delivered one-to-one and group teachings, maintaining student engagement and enthusiasm through subject passion and effective communication.
- Planned and executed innovative lessons to improve students reading, writing and understanding skills through different techniques.

HERMES LOGISTIC - ACCIONA - LOGISTIC OPERATIONS MANAGER

Madrid, Spain

2006 - 2012

- Supervised all facets of routine deliveries by effectively routing loads, managing drivers and meeting DFT requirements.
- Maintained workplace safety by involving employees in order to maximize engagement to team morale.
- Ensure staff followed administrative policies and compliance regulations by closely monitoring daily operations and performing safety audits.